[
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            2
        ],
        "question": "How many features are in the original dataset?",
        "answer": "226",
        "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            3
        ],
        "question": "How many rows are in the original dataset?",
        "answer": "99999",
         "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
         "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            8
        ],
        "question": "How many columns have more than 70% missing values?",
       "answer": "There are 40 features having more than 70% missing value",
        "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
         "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
     {
      "cell_ids": [
         12
        ],
        "question": "How many rows were dropped based on having tenure equals to zero",
         "answer": "7745",
        "task": "Data Imputation",
         "skill": "MICE"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            15
        ],
        "question": "After dropping columns having more than 70% missing values, how many columns remain in the dataset?",
        "answer": "187",
        "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
  {
    "cell_ids": [
      19
    ],
    "question": "How many rows were there in total having missing values for the variables?",
    "answer": "There are 381 rows in total having missing values for these variables.",
      "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
      "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
  },
  {
        "cell_ids": [
            22
        ],
        "question": "After removing rows with all missing values in 89 features what is the shape of the dataframe?",
          "answer": "(99618, 187)",
          "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
          "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
  {
    "cell_ids": [
      34
    ],
    "question": "What are the names of the new features created using average recharge amount?",
      "answer": "['avg_rech_amt_6', 'avg_rech_amt_7', 'avg_rech_amt_8', 'avg_rech_amt_9']",
      "task": "Feature Importance Ranking",
      "skill": "Random Forest Importance"
  },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            40
        ],
        "question": "How many high-value customers are present in the dataset?",
        "answer": "29937",
        "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
  {
    "cell_ids": [
      42
    ],
    "question": "What is the churn rate for high-value customers after tagging churners?",
    "answer": "8.09%",
     "task": "Churn Analysis",
     "skill": "Random Forest"
  }
]